我们得赶紧收尾了   琳
We got to wrap this up, Lin.
这对我们的生意可没好处
I mean, it's not great for business.
我们几乎把柜台给毁了
We totally screwed up the counter.
而且还没比出个结果
And nothing's settled.
反而引发了更多的问题
If anything, we've raised more questions.
我们依然是平局
I'm gonna say we're still even.
只剩最后一招了
And there's only one thing left.
菜刀对铁锤
Knife against hammer!
铁锤对菜刀
Hammer against knife!
铁对铁
Metal against metal!
不行  我们不来了
No way. We're-we're done.
平局也蛮好
A tie is good.
是的  鲍勃那么爱他那把刀
Yeah, Bob loves his knife.
我可不想毁了它
I'd hate to destroy it.
我的刀就是用铁锤做的  泰迪
My knife was made with hammers, Teddy.
用铁锤敲只会让它更结实
Hammering would actually make it stronger, so...
你尽管自我安慰吧
Whatever you want to tell yourself.
我先来
I get to go first!
五秒一局  开始
Five second rounds. Go!
芙纪绳  上
Fukinawa, go!